olx.fr 2017-06-06

# Privacy statement - Welcome to the OLX career site

**PRIVACY POLICY: ONLINE CLASSIFIEDS  
OLX BV’s USER PRIVACY POLICY**

Below, some words about our privacy policy. If you have questions about our policy, [please get in contact with us](mailto:%20privacy@olx.com?subject=I%20have%20a%20question%20about%20your%20privacy%20policy).  

**1.      SCOPE &  CONSENT**

This Privacy Policy describes our practices with respect to personal data collected via our website www.joinolx.com and www.olx.com, mobile applications and associated services and tools, where users may engage in activities such as register with us, create a profile, submit personal information and CV´s, exchange messages and perform a host of associated functions. In all cases we shall comply with applicable provisions of data protection law in the jurisdictions where we operate. This Privacy Policy is subject to the laws of the Netherlands.  
By using our website, downloading our mobile application, and/or using any associated services and tools where this Privacy Policy appears, you are deemed to have read, understood and given consent to our use of your personal data consistent with this Privacy Policy and with our Terms of Use.

You should be aware that when you click certain links on our website or within our app you could be directed to other companies’ properties outside of our hosted environment where the information collected is outside of our direct control. The privacy policy of the third parties’ properties or applications will govern the information obtained from you by these third parties in those contexts.

**2.       INFORMATION WE COLLECT, RECEIVE AND HOST**

Profile Information: When users contact us through this site, we may require certain information such as name, telephone number, CV. You should carefully consider the risks of making certain personal information—particularly information such as address or precise location information—publicly available. Where a user has decided to login to our site using a third-party authentication service such as Facebook Connect, we may also receive additional profile or other information authorized by that provider.

Website and Mobile Data: We may automatically receive and log information on our servers from your browser or device including your IP address, software and hardware attributes, pages that you request, mobile identifiers, information about app usage, and other device or systems-level information. This can occur on our website or mobile app, or on third parties’ services.

Appended Information: We may also append information we lawfully obtain from business partners or third parties to existing data we hold about our users.

**3.       IP ADDRESS, COOKIES & MOBILE IDENTIFIERS:**

We may collect certain information through technology like cookies, pixels and local storage (like on your browser or device). Cookies are small text files that store information on your computer, mobile phone or other device locally. Pixels are small images that are part of codes on webpages that do things like allow another server to measure viewing of a webpage and often are used in connection with cookies. The code trackes if and when (and on which page) a pixel is loaded to indicate that a user has engaged with a specific screen or portion of a screen.

With the help of cookies, the web server can save, for instance, preferences and settings on the user’s computer, mobile phone or other device which are then automatically restored on the next visit. Or to put it another way, the cookies are used, among other things, to make the use of the site more user-friendly so that, for instance, you do not have to repeat the log-in process when you visit again. We use both persistent cookies and session cookies. Whereas persistent cookies remain on your computer for a longer period of time, session cookies are automatically deleted when the browser window is closed.

We may allow third parties such as advertising or analytics providers to collect information using these types of technologies directly on our website or from our mobile application. The data that they collect is subject to the applicable privacy policy of those third parties.

**4.       USE OF THIS INFORMATION**

To provide our service we may use the information we collect and host for the following general purposes:

(i) to provide services to job seekers, including to create and manage applications, to resolve technical difficulties and to enable features;

(ii) to customize offers and experiences, including advertising on our properties or third parties’ properties;

(iii) to monitor general and individual user activity and to manage traffic on the Website;

(iv) to undertake research initiatives and to perform analytics to improve our services; and

(vi) to enforce our Terms of Use including to combat fraud and abuse.

We may retain information that we collect and observe on our network only for as long as is required to fulfill the above business objectives.

**5.       INFORMATION SHARING**

We may share information we collect with our affiliates (companies under common ownership and control) located in any third country. These companies may only process and use this information to assist us for purposes described above and are bound to honor this Privacy Policy.

We do not share personal information about our users with non-affiliated third parties unless we have our users’ specific permission to do so, or in the following circumstances:

We may use third-party service providers to assist in offering aspects of our services, in which case they shall have no authority to independently use any personal information they process on our behalf, and shall be subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  
We reserve the right to share information with private or public authorities that will enable us to fight fraud and abuse on our network, to investigate suspected violations of law, or to fight any other suspected breach of our terms of service.

We may share personal information with government authorities as required by applicable law.

As a matter of policy we do not rent or sell personal information about our users with non-affiliated third parties unless we have our users’ specific permission to do so. In the event that our business or a division of our business is reorganized or sold and we transfer all or substantially all of our assets to a new owner, your personal information may be transferred to the buyer to enable continuity of service.

We may share certain non-personal information (data that does not identify our users individually) with third-party service providers, trusted partners or approved researchers in order to better understand what advertisements or services may interest you, to improve the overall quality and effectiveness of our services or their services, or to contribute to academic research that we believe is of broader social benefit.

**6.       USER CONTROLS**

Correction and Deletion:

For users that have created an account or listing with us, you can access, correct or delete the information you provided by accessing the Website and following the deletion instructions for your CV. You are responsible for keeping the data you provide or post on our network accurate. If your account was created through an identity provider (e.g. on Facebook.com) you may also disable or change the account information through the settings offered by the identity provider.

Cookies: Most major desktop and mobile web browsers (eg Safari, Firefox, Internet Explorer, Chrome, Opera) provide controls that allow you to limit or block the setting of cookies on your systems. Note that disabling cookies in your browser for either first-party domains (the sites you actively visit) or third-party domains (companies other than those you directly visit on the Web) may result in decreased functionality in certain instances.

**7.       SECURITY**

All information we collect is protected by reasonable technical means and reasonable security procedures in order to prevent unauthorized access or use of data. Our affiliates, trusted partners and third-party service providers have committed to manage the information in accordance with our requirements for security and privacy.

**8.       CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 1 November 2015. We may update this Policy from time to time.  By continuing to use our services after that period our customers confirm their continuing acceptance of any updates to this Privacy Policy.

**9.       CONTACT INFORMATION**  
Questions about this privacy policy can be sent to [privacy@olx.com](mailto:%20privacy@olx.com?subject=I%20have%20a%20question%20about%20your%20privacy%20policy).
